{
    "id": "10d6f8e464474f35a21558914b1064de",
    "title": "Somebody, Anybody, Nobody, Nowhere etc.",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "15d014ee83994033a7bd054643102527",
            "title": "Somebody, Anybody, Somewhere, Anywhere",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did …………………………. phone when I was out?",
                    "description": "We use anybody in questions and negative sentences.",
                    "answers": [
                        "anybody",
                        "somebody",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s go ………………………….. quiet.",
                    "description": "We use somewhere in affirmative sentences.",
                    "answers": [
                        "somewhere",
                        "anywhere"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I searched for him everywhere but I couldn’t find him …………………………",
                    "description": "We use anywhere in negative sentences.",
                    "answers": [
                        "anywhere",
                        "somewhere"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I feel like eating ………………………… hot.",
                    "description": "We use something in affirmative clauses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "anything",
                        "something"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t do …………………………… yesterday.",
                    "description": "We use anything in negative clauses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "anything",
                        "something"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does …………………….. know where Michael lives?",
                    "description": "Anyone means the same as anybody.",
                    "answers": [
                        "anyone",
                        "anybody",
                        "someone",
                        "somebody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can borrow ………………………….. book at a time.",
                    "description": "Any one means any single one.",
                    "answers": [
                        "anyone",
                        "any one",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I took ………………………. to repair the car.",
                    "description": "\r\nSome time can mean quite a lot of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "sometime",
                        "some time",
                        "sometimes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s meet ………………………… next week.",
                    "description": "Sometime can mean one day.",
                    "answers": [
                        "sometime",
                        "some time",
                        "sometimes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………… visited them when I was in Mumbai.",
                    "description": "Sometimes can mean on some occasions.",
                    "answers": [
                        "sometime",
                        "some time",
                        "sometimes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. that year, granny had a heart attack.",
                    "description": "\r\nEarly means near the beginning of the period of time we are talking about\r\n",
                    "answers": [
                        "Early",
                        "Soon",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hope you can finish the work ……………………………..",
                    "description": "Soon can mean a short time after now.",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}